Ton Geatman



jonlyeatman@gmail.com



github.com/Yeatmans1



COMMERCE TWP, MI





404-423-7274



http://www.jonlyeatman.com

SUMMARY

Full-Stack Developer with a passion for UI/UX design focusing on an exceptional experience for end-all users. As an experienced business owner comes a strong understanding of business operations, the importance of teamwork and detailed planning. Having come from a graphics background I create a strong bridge between web development and design for the overall brand process.

Strengths: Leadership, Out-of-the-Box Thinking, Strategic, Highly-Motivated

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Git, GitHub, HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Material-UI, JavaScript, React, jQuery, APIs, JSON, AJAX, Responsive Design, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, Sequelize, MVC, Handlebars

Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Figma, Microsoft Office,

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Development Certification, 2021 MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY, Lansing, MI

PROJECTS

WallPro | Deployed Link: http://www.WallPro.net | Repository: https://github.com/mbussert/shaw-ppc

A full-stack web application created in React to assist clients in calculating square footage measurements for wall installation material deliverables on behalf of the design company. Uses Sass, MySQL, Material-UI, JavaScript, NodeMailer, React Player, Express, Node.js

Axios, Sequelize, Passport

Treat Yo'Shelf | Deployed Link: https://github.com/hstor3/treat-yo-shelf
A user-friendly app that lets you organize your books and treat your bookshelf utilizing HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Handlebars

DinGen | Deployed Application: https://yeatman51.github.io/dingen-web/ A web application built in an agile team environment aiming to simplify a user's decision-making process for dinner selection. This application leverages two third-party APIs, HTML, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, jQuery UI Library & Font Awesome

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Owner/Operator

Phoenix Custom Printing, LLC 2018 - Present

Graphic Design Artist

Superior Edge Leather Works, LLC 2017 - 2019

Infantryman

Michigan Army National Guard 2013 - 2017

- Had a company standard of 100% production quality/error handling
- Maximized immediate turn-around by minimizing unnecessary overhead
- Partnered with local third-party vendors to create a streamline process for clients
- Quality relationship building with clients for trustworthy product delivery
- Consistently delivered close to 500 designs quarterly per clientele
- Optimized processes working with a variety of garments, inks and merchandise
- Streamlined production pipeline for multi faceted items
- Displayed a high level of competence and professionalism under stressful situations
- Supervised, trained and ensured the safety and welfare of a 4-person team, maintaining a 100% safety record